Life doesn't have to be perfect for love to be extraordinary.
The Fault in Our Stars is a romance, drama film directed by Josh Boone.
Despite the tumor-shrinking medical miracle that has bought her a few years, Hazel has
never been anything but terminal, her final chapter inscribed upon diagnosis.
But when a patient named Augustus Waters suddenly appears at Cancer Kid
Support Group, Hazel's story is about to be completely rewritten.
Hazel Grace Lancaster, played by Shailene Woodley.
Augustus Waters, played by Ansel Elgort.
Isaac, played by Nat Wolff.
Frannie Lancaster, played by Laura Dern.
Michael Lancaster, played by Sam Trammell.
Peter van Houten, played by Willem Dafoe.
The Fault in Our Stars is a 2014 American coming-of-age romantic drama film directed
by Josh Boone from a screenplay by Scott Neustadter and Michael H.
Weber, based on the 2012 novel of the same name by John Green.
The film stars Shailene Woodley and Ansel Elgort, with Laura Dern, Sam
Trammell, Nat Wolff, and Willem Dafoe in supporting roles.
The story centers on a sixteen-year-old cancer patient, played by Woodley, forced by her parents to attend a support
group, where she meets and subsequently falls in love with another cancer patient, played by Elgort.
Development began in January 2012 when Fox 2000 Pictures optioned the film
adaptation rights to adapt the novel into a feature film.
Principal photography began on August 26, 2013, in Pittsburgh, with a few additional
days in Amsterdam, The Netherlands, before concluding on October 16.
Pittsburgh doubled for all of the scenes set in Indianapolis, Indiana, the
novel's setting, as well as for some interior scenes set in Amsterdam.
The Fault in Our Stars had its premiere at the Seattle International Film Festival on May 16, 2014, and was released in the United States on June 6 by 20th
Century Fox to favorable reviews, with praise being given to Woodley's and Elgort's performances and chemistry together, as well as the screenplay.
The film opened at number one at the box office during its opening weekend and grossed
$307.2 million worldwide against a production budget of $12 million.
It was released on DVD and Blu-ray on September 16, 2014, and
earned $42 million in total domestic video sales.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, support group,
amsterdam, netherlands, cancer, valentine's day.
The tone is emotional.